And I'd give up forever to touch you
'Cause I know that you feel me somehow
You're the closest to heaven
that I'll ever be
And I don't wanna go home right now
And all I can taste is this moment
And all I can breathe is your life
When sooner or later it's over
I just don't wanna miss you tonight
And I don't want the world to see me
'Cause I don't think that
they'd understand
When everything's made to be broken
I just want you to know who I am
And you can't fight the tears
that ain't coming
Or the moment of truth in your lies
When everything feels like the movies
Yeah, you bleed just to
know you're alive
And I don't want the world to see me
'Cause I don't think that
they'd understand
When everything's made to be broken
I just want you to know who I am
And I don't want the world to see me
'Cause I don't think that
they'd understand
When everything's made to be broken
I just want you to know who I am
And I don't want the world to see me
'Cause I don't think that
they'd understand
When everything's made to be broken
I just want you to know who I am